My Little Pony: Best Gift Ever is a animation, comedy,
fantasy film directed by Jim Miller.
As the ponies prepare for another Hearth's Warming, families come together to celebrate the holiday; Pinkie Pie, Fluttershy,
Applejack, Rarity, and Rainbow Dash are ready for the big day, but Princess Twilight Sparkle doesn't have time to celebrate.
Twilight Sparkle (voice), played by Tara Strong.
Pinkie Pie / Fluttershy / Pony Shopper (voice), played by Andrea Libman.
Applejack / Rainbow Dash / Pony Vendor 2 (voice), played by Ashleigh Ball.
Spike (voice), played by Cathy Weseluck.
Rarity / Muffins / Flurry Heart (voice), played by Tabitha St. Germain.
Discord (voice), played by John de Lancie.
My Little Pony: Best Gift Ever (also known as My Little Pony: Best Gift Ever!
and My Little Pony: Friendship is Magic: Best Gift Ever) is a double-length Christmas-themed special based on the
animated television series My Little Pony: Friendship Is Magic, taking place in-between seasons eight and nine.
It premiered on October 27, 2018 on Discovery Family.
In this special, Twilight Sparkle and her friends do a "Hearth's Warming Helper" to get just one Hearth's
Warming present for another pony, to which they race all over Equestria to find the perfect gift.
The tone is lighthearted.